STEPHEN DOE

323 Park Place Irvington, New Jersey, 07111 201-658-9309 redcard1016@yahoo.com

There are gaps in my resume when it comes to my education and work experience that need to be addressed. My educational background is tricky to explain because it doesn't flow in a straight line. If it were given visual representation it would look more like the dashed and dotted lines found on a highway. I graduated from Irvington High School then spent a few semesters at Essex County College followed by a few more semesters at Kean University, but was unable to finish my degree in broadcast communications because I had a nervous breakdown.

Since I was twelve I've suffered from Agoraphobia, a severe social anxiety disorder that made it tough for me to go outdoors for long stretches of time and interact with people, and it all caught up with me when I was in college, so from about 2003 to 2014 I had to be creative in the ways that I made a living while I tried to deal with my disorder.

For years I was a merchant on both Amazon and Ebay where I had to deal with getting orders out on time and with conflict resolution when it came to dealing with customers. Many people like to buy things on Ebay then look for any excuse to file a dispute so they can get out of paying for merchandise and I was able to win all of my disputes and put out those fires before they spread.

I've also spent years as a freelance writer where I copy-edited articles and manuscripts for clients. I've also provided content for web pages in the form of SEO or "Search Engine Optimization " articles which helped drive traffic to my clients webpages.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Writer, Aug 2008 – Present Amazon Merchant 2002-2008 Ebay Merchant 2002-2008

EDUCATION

Essex County College, Newark, NJ 2000 – 2001

Major: Broadcast Communications

Kean University, Union, NJ 2001 – 2003

Major: Broadcast Communications

Rutgers Coding Bootcamp April to October 2016

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap
JQuery
JavaScript
Typing
Search Engine Optimization
Copy Editing

Sales